{
    "subject": "Robert_Sterling",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Ann_Sothern",
    "human_readable": "Robert Sterling is married to Ann Sothern.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.984643816947937,
            "question": "Are Robert Sterling and Ann Sothern a married couple?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9827309250831604,
            "question": "Who are the spouses of Robert Sterling and Ann Sothern?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9679603576660156,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the marriage between Robert Sterling and Ann Sothern?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8734057545661926,
            "question": "Do you know anything about the relationship between Robert Sterling and Ann Sothern?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8732675313949585,
            "question": "Who is Robert Sterling married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6724295616149902,
            "question": "Who is Ann Sothern?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6361759901046753,
            "question": "Is Robert Sterling in a relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.634670078754425,
            "question": "What is the name of Robert Sterling's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5832995176315308,
            "question": "What is the name of Ann Sothern's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30937033891677856,
            "question": "Is there any information about Robert Sterling's personal life?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Robert Sterling is married to Ann Sothern.",
            "html": "yago_11088_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Ann Sothern's husband?",
            "html": "yago_11088_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Robert Sterling's wife?",
            "html": "yago_11088_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Robert Sterling in a relationship?",
            "html": "yago_11088_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11088_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11088_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11088_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11088_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11088_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11088_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11088_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11088_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11088_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11088_67.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. Specifically, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_11088/re-ranker-msmarco/105.txt mentions that Ann Sothern was previously married to Robert Sterling (1943 - 1949)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Robert Sterling was married to Ann Sothern from 1943 to 1949, and they had a daughter named Tisha. This confirms the marital relationship between Robert Sterling and Ann Sothern as stated in the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}